

Objective

Delivering beyond the client's expectations while still presenting practical, efficient solutions is something that I always strive to accomplish. I want to work for people who invest me in their processes and take advantage of the creativity and experience that I can offer.

Work History

■ Pearson Performance Solutions - Graphic Designer/Illustrator - (1998-present)

The wide variety of responsibilities that I have at PPS include:

- Art lead on small to medium sized projects
- Design GUIs for proposals, prototypes, and projects
- Custom illustration and animation by hand, Flash, or 3D
- Brainstorm games, coach characters, and other concepts with clients
- Create or modify Flash interactions
- Provide decorative or instructional content artwork
- Work on several jobs for a variety of customers simultaneously

■ Ethermoon Entertainment - Art Lead/Video Game Artist - (2000-2002)

While maintaining my level of effort and quality of work at my full-time job, I helped to complete an independently produced Real-Time Strategy game for the PC.

- Designed a variety of game characters and produced the models and any animation sequences for those characters
- Created, finished and published a computer strategy game with a handful of hardworking people from all around the world
- Created standards, met deadlines, and managed another artist on the project

■ Reynolds & Reynolds - Forms Designer - (1995-1998)

My first full time design job after college required precise adherence to corporate design standards in designing forms for our office's main client, PNC Bank. Other responsibilities included:

- Designed various marketing mailers, posters, and brochures
- Worked closely with our primary printers to proof and produce finished pieces
- Designed electronic forms for the various bank branches

■ Freelance - Graphic Design/Illustration/Animation - (1993-present)

For the past 10 years, I've designed, illustrated and animated a variety of print, electronic and interactive pieces for clients including websites, posters, coach characters, 3D illustration, 3D animation, flash animation, flash interactions, technical artwork, brochures, logos, and more.

Education

Additional training - Attended workshops in advanced Flash and 3D (1999-2000)

LaRoche College - Bachelor of Science in Graphic Design - 3.50 QPA (*Graduated* 1995)

Norwin High School - (Graduated 1991)

PGSA Scholarship - (Completed 1990)

Other Skills

- 3D Modeling and Animation
- Character Design
- Graphic Design for Web and Print (CDs, brochures, posters, etc.)
- HTML and Basic JavaScript
- Illustration
- Interface Design (web and CBT)
- Photography
- Storyboarding for Animations and Interactive concepts

Clients

- Adaptec
- AT&T
- Canon
- Campbells
- Citizens Bank
- HUD
- Merck
- National City
- Pacificare
- Pearson Education
- Pfizer
- PNC Bank
- Qwest
- SBC
- Tetra
- VerizonZebra Technologies

Software

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe ImageReady
- Adobe PageMaker
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Premiere
- Discreet 3DS Max
- Macromedia DirectorMacromedia Dreamweaver
- Macromedia Flash
- Microsoft Office

Honors & Awards

3D Illustrations and training published in the "3DS Max Bible" (versions 3, 4 & 6) by Kelly Murdock (1999-2003)

Top ten finalist at the 2001 Independent Game Festival (2001)

Technology Services Project Recognition Award for a Qwest OOR Project (2001)

Government Technology Leadership Award recognition for contribution to a HUD 2020 project (1999)

Graduated with Honors, member of Dean's List (1993-1995)

References available upon request.